A Guide to the Papers of the Virginia Quarterly Review, 1925-1935
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Markum, Leo 1925-1929, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Marley, Harold P. 1929-1934, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Martin, Everett Dean 1931, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Martin, William 1929-1933, 26 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Marvin, George 1927-1930, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Mason, Daniel Gregory 1925-1934, 27 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Mason, Francis Claiborne 1926-1933, 19 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Massey, Vincent 1929-1930, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Masson, Thomas Lansing 1929-1931, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Masters, Edgar Lee 1932, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Matthews, Brander 1925 [June 8], 2 pages. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Matthews, Thomas S. 1929-1931, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Mattick, Paul 1934, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Maurice, Frederick 1934-1936, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Maury, Reuben 1934, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 31)
- Mayer, Frederick P. 1925-1934, ca. 125 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Maynard, Theodore 1925-1933, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Mayo, Bernard 1933, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Mencken, Henry Louis 1924-1934, 42 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Metcalf, John Calvin 1926-1933, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Metcalf, Maynard M. 1929, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Millard, Clifford I. 1929-1931, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Millay, Edna St. Vincent 1927 June 28, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Millay (Box 32)
- Miller, Francis Pickens 1930-1934, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Miller, Harry Edward 1925-1934, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Miller, Helen Hill 1930-1935, ca. 100 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Milling, Chapman J. 1932-1934, 19 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Millis, Walter 1933, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Milton, George Fort 1925-1935, 91 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Mims, Edwin 1925-1928, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Minor, Charles L. 1925, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Minton, Balch, & Co. 1928-1934, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Mirrielees, Edith R. 1933-1934, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Mirsky, D.S. 1931-1933, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Mitchell, Broadus 1926-1935, ca. 125 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Mitchell, Langdon 1927-1928, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 32)
- Moffett, Cleveland 1925, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Mok, P.K. 1932, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Molyneux, Peter 1933 December 21, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Molyneux (Box 33)
- Monroe, Harriet 1925-1934, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Montague, Margaret Prescott 1924-1935, 41 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Montgomery, Roselle Mercier 1928-1933, 21 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Moody, Minnie Hite 1931-1935, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Moody, Paul D. 1929 December 2, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Moody (Box 33)
- Moore, Alvin Edward 1929-1932, 20 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Moore, Marianne 1927 February 24, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Moore, R. Walton 1927, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Moore, Virginia 1926-1933, 32 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Moreland, John Richard 1926-1935, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Morgan, George 1929, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Morgan, Marshall 1935, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Morley, Christopher 1932-1935, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Morley, Felix 1931-1933, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Morrill, Lily Logan 1931-1934, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Morris, Robert L. 1929-1934, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- William Morrow & Co., Inc. 1927-1934, 43 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Morton, David 1935, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Morton, Rosalie Slaughter 1934-1935, 22 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Motes, Isaac H. 1930-1934, 21 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Mowrer, Edgar A. 1926, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Mullins, Helene 1925-1931, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Mumford, Lewis 1927-1935, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Munroe, Vernon, Jr. 1934, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Munson, Gorham Bert 1929-1935, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Murchison, Claudius 1929-1935, ca. 100 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Murdaugh, J.E. Dandridge 1926-1928, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Murdock, Kenneth B. 1929, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Myers, Walter L. 1927-1935, 76 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 33)
- Miscellaneous M 1925-1935, ca. 600 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 34)
- Naft, Stephen 1930-1931, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Nelson, Wilbur A. 1926-1933, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Nevill, Florence 1929-1933, 14 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Newcomb, John Lloyd 1927-1930, 2 items. Letters to Newcomb (Box 35)
- Newman, Oliver P. 1926-1931, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Newton, Alfred Edward 1925, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Newton, Joseph Fort 1926 April 19, 1 l. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Nickerson, Hoffman 1934, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Nin, Anaïs 1931, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Nixon, H.C. 1929-1935, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Nock, Albert Jay 1929-1932, 41 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Norfleet, Fillmore 1934, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- University of North Carolina Press 1926-1935, 30 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Northrop, F.S.C. 1932-1935, 23 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- W.W. Norton and Co. 1929-1935, 21 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Notestein, Wallace 1935, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Novak, Sonia 1929-1933, 39 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Nowell, Elizabeth 1935, 34 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Nunn, William L. 1932-1934, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Miscellaneous N 1925-1935, ca. 150 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 35)
- Ober, Harold 1931-1934, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- O'Brien, Edward J[oseph]1925-1932, 18 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- O'Brien, Frederick 1925 April 8, 1 l. Letter, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- O'Brien, Justin 1931, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- O'Donnell, George Marion 1934-1935, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- Odum, Howard Washington 1925-1934, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- O'Faolain, Sean 1927-1935, 34 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- Oliphant, H.C. 1928, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- Orr, Oliver 1929-1934, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- O'Shea, Deirdre 1925-1930, 22 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- O'Sheel, Shaemas 1927, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- Overton, Grant 1929, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- Owens, Hamilton 1931, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- Owsley, Frank L. 1934-1935, 28 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- Oxford University Press 1925-1935, 81 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- Miscellaneous O 1925-1935, ca. 100 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 36)
- Pach, Walter 1925-1935, 21 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Page, James Morris 1927-1929, 8 items. Letters, Virginia Quarterly Review to Page (Box 37)
- Page, Thomas Walker 1929-1930, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Paget Literary Agency 1925-1935, 33 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Parker, Cornelia Stratton 1925 April 16, 1 l. Letter, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Parmenter, Catherine 1928-1930, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Parmenter, Christine 1931 March 30, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Parmenter (Box 37)
- Parks, Edd Winfield 1930-1935, 40 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Parry, Albert 1935, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Parsons, Alice Beal 1932-1933, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Patchen, Kenneth 1934, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Paterson, Isabel 1929-1934, 4 items. Letters, Virginia Quarterly Review to Paterson (Box 37)
- Patrick, G.M. 1925, 8 items. Letters, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Patterson, Frances Taylor 1931-1935, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Patton, John Shelton 1924-1929, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Payne, Abney 1925-1927, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Payne, Anne Blackwell 1925-1933, 32 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Pearl, Raymond 1927-1929, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Peck, Walter E. 1927, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Pennell, Madge 1930, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- University of Pennsylvania Press 1928, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Percy, William Alexander 1925-1930, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Perkins, Dexter 1930-1935, 55 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Perry, Bliss 1925 January 9, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Peterkin, Julia 1929-1935, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Pfister, Clara 1928-1934, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Philips, Ulrich 1930-1933, 21 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Pierson, W.W., Jr. 1929 January 25, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Pierson (Box 37)
- Pinckney, Josephine 1929-1935, 19 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- James B. Pinker and Son, Inc. 1928-1935, ca. 150 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Piper, Edwin Ford 1929-1930, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Pipkin, Charles W. 1927-1935, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 37)
- Podolsky, Edward 1928-1935, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Poe, Clarence 1927-1934, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- RE: Poe, Edgar Allan 1928-1930, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Porcher, Mary F. Wickham 1925-1928, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Porter, Charlotte Endymion 1924-1930, 6 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Porter, Katherine Anne 1926-1935, 33 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Porter, Kenneth Wiggins 1930-1935, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Porterfield, Allen W. 1925-1934, 53 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Pound, Louise 1929, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Pound, Roscoe 1925-1929, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Powell, Diana Kearny 1930-1935, 22 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Powys, Llewelyn 1929-1935, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Pratt, Theodore 1935, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Preston, John Hyde 1926-1931, 65 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Pringle, Henry Powles 1932, 18 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Princeton University Press 1934, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Priest, George M. 1925 February 14, 1 l. Letter, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Pokosch, Frederic 1927-1934, 38 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Pulsifer, Harold Trowbridge 1930-1932, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- George Palmer Putnam, Inc. 1927-1934, 26 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Pym, Michael 1925-1926, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Miscelleneous P 1925-1935, ca. 600 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 38)
- Quick, Dorothy 1931-1932, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Quigley, Harold Scott 1925-1935, 40 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Quinn, Arthur Hobson 1927-1928, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Miscellaneous Q 1927-1935, 14 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Ramsey, Robert L. 1926-1930, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Random House 1931-1935, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Ransom, John Crowe 1929-1935, 40 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Ransom, Seymour 1930 September 22, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Ransom (Box 39)
- Rascoe, Burton 1929-1933, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Rawlings, Marjorie Kinnan 1935 January 16, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Rawlings (Box 39)
- Raymond, Dora Neill 1932, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Reade, Frank R. 1926-1935, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Rede, Kenneth 1925-1928, 20 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Reese, Lizette Woodworth 1925-1935, 35 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Repplier, Agnes 1925, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Rice, Cale Young 1925-1932, 45 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Rice, Laban Lacy January 14, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Richards, Albert A. 1935, 5 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Richards, J.A. 1935 December 19, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Richards (Box 39)
- Richardson, Eudora Ramsay 1928-1932, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Ringrose Hyacinthe 1926-1929, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Ripley, Clements 1933, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Ritter, Margaret Tod 1927-1934, 19 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Rittenhouse, Jessie Belle ca. 1925, 6 items. Letters, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Roberts, Elizabeth Madox 1930-1935, 15 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Roberts, John Hawley 1933-1934, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Roberts, Morley 1930, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Robinson, Edwin Arlington 1927-1931, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Robinson, William Henry 1925 March 3, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Rockefeller, John D., Jr. 1928 November 8, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Rodman, Selden 1931, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Roethke, Theodore 1932-1935, 27 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Rogers, Lindsay 1924-1933, 23 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Roller, Bert 1927-1928, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Rourke, Constance 1935, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Roy, Dunbar 1932-1933, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 39)
- Rucker, Katharine 1931-1932, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 40)
- Ruhl, Arthur 1927-1929, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 40)
- Rukeyser, Muriel 1934, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 40)
- Rusk, William Sener 1929-1935, 60 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 40)
- Russell, Bertrand 1929 December 31, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Russell (Box 40)
- Russell, Frances Theresa 1930-1932, 13 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 40)
- Russell, George William 1925 January 2, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 40)
- Russell, Philips 1932-1934, 19 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 40)
- Rutledge, Archibald 1925-1935, 91 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 40)
- Miscellaneous R 1925-1935, ca. 450 items. Miscellaneous authors. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 40)
- Sabin, Edwin 1925 March 3, 1 l. Letter, to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Saffold, Mildred Reynolds 1929, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Salls, Helen 1925-1931, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Salpeter, Harry 1934-1935, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Sandburg, Carl 1927-1928, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Sass, Herbert Ravenal 1934-1935, 21 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Saxon, Lyle 1927 September 19, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Saxon (Box 41)
- Schauffler, Robert Haven 1925-1932, 12 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Schelling, Felix 1930-1931, 9 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Schmidt, Bernadotte 1926-1931, 19 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Scollard, Clinton 1927-1932, 37 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Charles Scribner's Sons 1927-1935, 57 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Scruggs, Anderson 1928-1935, 31 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Scruggs, Philip 1925-1935, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Seashore, Carl 1925 February 16, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Seitz, Don Carlos 1926-1930, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Severance, Margaret 1927, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Severence, Paul 1926-1931, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Seymour, Charles 1930-1934, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Shafer, Robert 1930-1932, 11 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Shannon, Edgar Finley 1925-1928, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Sharp, Dallas Lore 1925-1931, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Shaw, Elizabeth 1929-1932, 10 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Sheean, Vincent 1930, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Sheed and Ward, Inc. 1933-1934, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Sheldon, Edward 1929-1933, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Shepperson, Archibald Bolling 1933 March 14, 1 l. Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Shepperson (Box 41)
- Sherwood, Margaret 1925-1931, 4 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Shorey, Paul 1925 February 27, 1 l. Letter to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Siegfried, André 1929-1930, 3 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Simon and Schuster, Inc. 1927-1935, 23 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Simpson, James 1930-1931, 22 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Simpson, Violet A. 1927-1929, 18 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Sledd, Benjamin 1925-1934, 7 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Slosson, Edwin Emery 1924-1925, 2 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Harrison Smith and Robert Haas, Inc. 1932-1935, 16 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Smith, Henry 1935, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Smith, Logan Pearsall 1934, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Smith, Paul 1927-1929, 29 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Smith, Preserved 1934, 8 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Snavely, Tipton 1932-1933, 3 items. Letters to Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Snider, Charles Lee 1925-1931, 26 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Snow, Royall 1928-1929, 6 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Snow, Wilbert 1930-1935, 32 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Snyder, Carl 1934, 2 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)
- Soule, George 1930-1935, 17 items. Correspondence with Virginia Quarterly Review (Box 41)